There's a lot of controversy surrounding the
está pasando mucha polémica en torno al
birth of
al al ingreso del bebé de la hija de
Anabel Pantoja's daughter's baby and it shouldn't, the truth is, there
Anabel Pantoja y no debería la verdad no
shouldn't be so much controversy and so much
debería generarse tanta polémica y tanto
debate. But hey, when something
debate Pero bueno cuando pasa una cosa
viral happens, especially when it generates so much
viral no sobre todo que genera tanto
media interest, in the end there are
interés mediático al final sí hay
controversies, people who
polemiques lo hacen mejor gente que lo
do it better do it worse, people who think they do it
hacen peor gente que cree que lo hace
better and criticize those who think they
mejor y crítica a la que cree que lo
do it worse. So there's some
hace peor Entonces pues hay cierta
controversy, I don't know what you
polémica yo no sé ustedes qué es lo que
think, okay? I don't know if you want us to
pensáis vale No sé si queréis que
comment on that and this is the first
comentemos eso y así es el primer
excerpt before we get into the subject
extracto antes de meternos en en el tema
as such, I was tagged in this today you
como tal me etiquetaron en esto hoy me
tagged me in this and it wasn't with me.
etiquetaste en esto y conmigo no iba
But anyway, since what's up, since what's up, let's have our
Pero bueno ya que ya queé tal Ya queé
opinions, right? Javid. Speaking clearly.
tal opinamos no eh javid Hablando claro
There's someone with the sad subject of
Hay alguno con el triste tema de la hija
Anabel Pantoja's daughter who tells you that it's
de Anabel Pantoja que te dice que está
wrong. The way others report it and that it's
mal Cómo informan los demás y que está
very wrong to do a live broadcast because it creates
muy mal hacer un directo porque crea
alarm for the next day, do a
alarma para el día siguiente hac un
live broadcast for Anabel Pantoja's daughter
directo por la hija de Anabel Pantoja
but she has values ​​and such. And so on with everything, let's
pero tiene valores y tal Y así con todo
see, here there are people who were
a ver aquí hay gente que me estaba
tagging me, no, and then Javi more  down there it
etiquetando no y luego Javi más abajo
seems he has clarified it no no Hey, it's
como que lo ha aclarado no no Oye que
obviously not for Javi, no I mean, I did
por Javi no va evidentemente no O sea yo
n't say that
no he dicho eso
and I think what people are
e y yo creo que lo que la gente está
criticizing is this sad last hour of
criticando es esto triste última hora de
Anabel Pantoja's daughter they fear the worst
la hija de Anabel Pantoja temen lo peor
absolutely sad absolute sadness for
triste absoluta tristeza absoluta por la
Anabel Pantoja's daughter admitted to the
hija de Anabel Pantoja ingresada de
emergency room let's see in the other one This is for
urgencia a ver yo en la otra Esto va por
alber I mean I think there's no need for
alber o sea yo creo que no hace falta
Javi to name it's more than notorious
que Javi ponga nombre es más que notorio
and public that they maintain a
y público que ellos mantienen una un
bit of enmity they're talking I think it
pique enemistad están hablando Yo creo
's public and notorious that they
que es público y notorio que ellos
maintain a bit of enmity no and they
mantienen una una enemistad no y se
pull it off from time to time no and on
tiran pullit de vez en cuando no y en
this occasion I don't know what you
esta ocasión yo no sé usted de lo que
think I mm I have
pensáis yo mm tengo sentimientos
mixed feelings about this issue the other
encontrados con este tema en la otra
time they were also arguing
ocasión que estaban discutiendo también
about the thumbnail issue titles and such HM
sobre tema miniatura títulos y demás HM
I in I was more on Javi's side
yo en Yo sí que estaba más de parte de
of Speaking clearly but in this one I
Javi de Hablando claro pero en esta es
have feelings to find okay
que tengo sentimientos encontrar vale
because because one thing is
porque porque una cosa es
eh Let's see is the topic is the topic of the
eh A ver es el tema es el tema del
moment is the news okay
momento es la noticia vale
em but eh Ah let's see one thing is and I
em pero eh Ah a ver una cosa es y yo
think What is  I was referring to seeing one thing
creo A lo que se refería al ver una cosa
is that whether you make content or not,
es que tú hagas contenido o no hagas
on the subject, you're obviously going to
contenido sobre el tema evidentemente
be content on the subject, it's the
vas a ser contenido sobre el tema es la
news that everyone
noticia de la que todo el mundo ahora
wants to hear right now,
mismo quiere quiere escuchar
HM, for example, there are some
HM a mí por ejemplo hay algunos
headlines, I mean, I think that I think it's
titulares o sea yo creo que yo creo que
not about talking about the subject or it's not worth it.
no se trata de hablar del tema o no vale
I think it's about, uh, with what tone
Yo creo que se trata de eh Con qué tono
and with what form. With what headlines not to
y con qué forma Con qué titulares no
attract the audience, uh, I think it's
atraer a la audiencia eh yo creo que es
of interest, no, the indicator is clear,
de interés no el indicador está claro
they are the visits, maybe if you go
son las visitas a lo mejor si tú pasas
from having, uh, 13,000 visits to
de tener eh 13,000 visitas a que de
suddenly, this seemed to me the other day,
repente a mí esto me pareció el otro día
well, now we'll talk about this, okay,
bueno ahora hablaremos de Esto vale
devastated, critical situation,
devastados situación crítica
uh, urgent statement by Anabel's daughter. I don't
eh comunicado urgente por la hija de
see these headlines as that bad either, they don't fear for their
tampoco los veo tan mal no temen por su
lives, if they are, let's see. No, I put myself in
vida si es que a ver No yo me pongo en
people's situation, don't imagine,
la situación de la gente no imagínate
uh, if I were Anabel Pantoja, I would understand
eh yo si fuera Anabel Pantoja entendería
that all the media were talking about
que todos los medios estuviesen hablando
me,
de mí
HM, with headlines that weren't breaking news about
HM con titulares no última hora sobre el
Anabel Pantoja's daughter's health
estado de salud de la hija de Anabel
or concern about her
Pantoja o preocupación por el estado de
health.  of Anabel Pantoja's daughter but they
salud de la hija de Anabel Pantoja pero
fear for her life and to put her there
temen por su vida y ponerla ahí
crying there was one that I don't know who
llorando hubo uno que no sé quién lo
put it there was a headline that I don't know who put it that one did
puso hubo un titular que no sé quién lo
seem a bit
puso que ese sí que me pareció un poco
so-so to me it's the one about the
tal es el
leak The medical report of
de El de filtrado El parte médico de de
Anabel Pantoja's daughter That did seem a bit
la hija de anbel Pantoja Eso sí me
outrageous to me of course I
parecía un poco una barbaridad claro es
think the discussion here isn't whether I do
que yo creo aquí la discusión no es si
n't know what Albert said okay if you
no sé lo que ha dicho alber vale si me
send me the extract I'll put it in I do
mandáis el extracto lo pongo no sé qué
n't know what it is what a drag Really what a drag really what have you man man what are you man man how lazy what a
abierto no sé lo que era ya me lo ha
drag it's all day long
se pega todo el el día eh es que es todo
man how lazy really well nothing now what I had open here well it's already closed what I had open here I don't know what it was it's already closed by this special little person who sticks around all day
el día es que es todo el día tío bueno
long eh it's ...  search among all
más profundamente y buscar entre todas
the hours of live broadcasts to see what he
las horas de directo que es lo que ha
said I would never report
dicho yo nunca mandaría a reportar
anyone what's going on Lil about the
seguramente a nadie Qué pasa Lil lo del
medical report was Diego well let's see in the
parte médico fue Diego bueno a ver al
end everyone has their own condition and
final cada uno tiene su su condición y
their own way of doing things and that's it and
su manera de de hacer las cosas y ya
and always with all the issues
está y y siempre con todos los temas
these controversies always happen and it
siempre pasan estas polémicas y siempre
's always the same ones who are on one side
son los mismos los que están en un lado
the others who are on the other but
los otros los que están en otro pero yo
in this case I think that it's not about
en esta ocasión creo que no se trata
talking about the issue or exploiting an
de de hablar del tema o de explotar un
issue or not Let's see if I
tema o no A ver si yo fuera la Si yo
were Anabel Pantoja or someone who
fuera anbel Pantoja o alguien que
was going through that situation I
estuviera pasando por esa situación Yo
understand
entiendo
perfectly that the media is going to be bringing
perfectamente que los medios van a estar
out the news of the day okay And they're going to be
sacando la noticia del día vale Y van a
talking about this all day long it's
estar todo el día hablando de esto
not even worth it But it's not the same Maybe
incluso no vale Pero no es lo mismo A lo
if I come across
mejor si yo encuentro con titulares de
breaking headlines about
em última hora sobre el estado de salud
Anabel Pantoja's health status, Anabel
de Anabel Pantoja de la hija de Anabel
Pantoja's daughter and concern there's no
Pantoja e preocupación no hay
concern devastating even well
preocupación devastador incluso bueno
okay Yes it is devastating and But when she
vale Sí es devastador e Pero cuando ella
still hasn't said anything she hasn't released
Todavía no ha dicho nada no ha sacado
any statement and the
ningún comunicado y tal se filtra el
medical report is leaked they fear the worst they fear for their
parte médico temen lo peor temen por su
lives that type of comment I wouldn't
vida ese tipo de comentari ya no me
sit down  I would think it would be a little bit not a
sentaría yo me parecería un poco no un
little bit like that [ __ ] I don't know what I had
poco así [__] No sé qué es lo que tenía
open here in this tab man I haven't been
aquí abierto en esta pestaña tío no he
able to see haha ​​What is Artura man
podido ver ja que Qué es artura tío de
really What is Artura Eh nobody knows Juani
verdad Qué es artura Eh no se sabe Juani
if ​​it's that I now let's go now
si es que yo ahora vamos a ir ahora
let's go a little bit to that okay now
vamos a ir un poco a a eso vale ahora
let's go a little bit to that that to me
vamos a ir un poco a eso que a mí me
seemed worse for example the issue of
pareció por ejemplo peor lo del tema de
Julio Iglesia that we talked about the other day
Julio Iglesia que comentamos el otro día
and especially when people
y sobre todo cuando la gente te lo
criticize you, you start insulting people
recrimina ponerte a insultar a la gente
Eh by Ah now I know what it was that I had
Eh por Ah ya sé lo que era lo que tenía
open in that tab [ __ ] What a shame Let's
abierta en esa pestaña [__] Qué pena A
see I can't open it again give me a
ver no la puedo volver a abrir darme un
second I know what it was They
segundo ya sé lo que era Es que a mí me
were criticizing me They
estaban criticando Es que a mí me
were criticizing me but
estaban criticando pero
because I'm not going to
por no lo voy a
find it what's up Pili if the headline
encontrar qué tal Pili si el titular
matches the content even a
coincide con el contenido aunque sea un
little bit it's all okay it's that it's the news it's that it
poco está todo okay es que es la noticia
's the news So I think it
es que es la noticia Entonces yo creo
depends a little bit on how far you
que depende un poco de hasta dónde
play with it Look the other day for
juegues con eso Mira el otro día por
example I think it was the one from Asturias they
ejemplo el creo que era el el de asturia
sent me a click that was
me mandaron un click que se estaba
justifying itself saying Ah but
justificando diciendo Ah pero
also  another issue that I see is
también otro tema que yo veo es el
my opinion if there are headlines there are
opinión mía si hay titulares hay
headlines I mean if things are happening and you have to
titulares O sea si están pasando cosas y
release 10 videos a day on the
tienes que sacar 10 vídeos un día del
same topic then you release 10 videos The
mismo tema pues sacas 10 vídeos El
problem is that you're releasing 10 videos
problema es que estés sacando 10 vídeos
when there aren't any you know that's where you can see the
cuando no los hay sabes ahí se te ve el
anxiety You can see the anxiety no but it's that
ansia Se te nota el ansia no pero si es
Anabel Pantoja I the subject of
que Anabel Pantoja yo el tema este de
Anabel Pantoja this these last hours
Anabel Pantoja esto estas últimas horas
not these last TR cu days that we have been dealing with it
no estos últimos TR cu días que llevamos
I have seen it
tratándolo yo lo he visto
to open obviously with that headline
para abrir evidentemente con ese titular
and that thumbnail eh on the subject eh but
y esa miniatura eh sobre el tema eh pero
without further ado let's review a little what has been
sin más repasamos un poco lo que se ha
said or what has come out which is very
dicho o lo que haya salido que es muy
little because it's that I tell you is that they
poco porque es que ya te digo es que
still haven't said almost
todavía no han dicho casillo no ha
the family hasn't come out to be an
salido la familia a ser un comunicado
official statement So there are no headlines,
oficial Entonces no hay titulares no
30 videos don't come out you know em
salen 30 vídeos me entiendes
But well each one has their way and
em Pero bueno cada uno tiene su forma y
each one has their thing it's a bit of the same old thing This was this
cada uno tiene su movida es un poco lo
was the tab
de siempre Este era esta era la pestaña
that I had closed is that it
que yo había cerrado es que me ha
seemed great to me because they
parecido buenísimo porque a mí a mí no
weren't criticizing me for dealing with the subject they
me estaban criticando por tratar el tema
were
a mí me estaban
criticizing me because  I put in the title
criticando porque lo puse en el título
last hour about the emergency admission
última hora sobre el ingreso de urgencia
of Pantoja's baby Okay and
del bebé de la Pantoja Vale y sin
yet within the live broadcast I talked about the
embargo dentro del directo hablé de del
subject okay this is clickbait he does it
tema vale esto es un clickbait lo hace a
daily he uses in the title the
diario usa en el título el drama de
Anabel Pantoja drama he speaks for 15 minutes
Anabel Pantoja habla 15 minutos
criticizing the others who comment on the
criticando a los demás que comentan el
subject it doesn't sound to me that I have criticized
tema no me suena que yo haya criticado
the others who comment on the subject in
los demás que comentas en el tema en
these days ago eh It doesn't sound to me eh I don't
estos días atrás eh No me suena eh No lo
know what to tell you and the rest of almost 3
sé decirme ustedes y el resto de casi 3
hours the topics are the messes he gets into
horas los temas son los líos donde se
and asking for money for lawsuits telesalseo channel
mete y pedir dinero para demandas canal
report well he is from Diego's community
denunciar bueno es de la comunidad de
and he doesn't like me Ah look share
Diego y no le caigo bien Ah mira
share these accounts the little
comparte comparte las cuentas estas el
angel the one who never takes down an account and
angelito el que nunca tumba cuenta y
asks for lawsuits will you know this nave del
pide para demandas sabrán esto nave del
Ah that they are tagging Iker and
Ah que están etiquetando a Iker y a
Carmen so they
Carmen para que lo
know Oh really Oh Oh Oh Ay this this has
sepan Ay de verdad Ay Ay Ay Ay este este
been great eh from del Wilson's account
ha sido buenísimo eh de la cuenta de del
jump such a jump that I
Wilson saltar una tal saltar que me he
got into his Twitter and it was all against
metido en su Twitter y era todo contra
me Twitter too eh jump says
mí el Twitter también eh saltar dice
what a drama he made with the license plate when it
vaya drama montó con la matrícula cuando
was exposed everywhere or  well
estaba expuesta por todas partes o sea
my license plate was exposed
mi matrícula estaba expuesta por todas
everywhere but not to me where do they have to how
partes pero no a mí a donde tienen que
soon Javi and I have to study
qu pronto Javi y yo tengo que estudiar
smiling face with a cold sweat a kiss
cara sonriendo con sudor frío un beso
Noa Well study because then you can watch the live broadcast later I
Noa Pues estudia que luego el directo lo
have a bit of a catarrh eh it
diferido tengo un poco de catarilla eh
shows no well that my license plate
se me nota no bueno que mi matrícula
was exposed everywhere okay
estaba expuesta por todas partes vale
I made a drama out of doing da he took it from
que yo hice drama por hacer da la cogió
live videos and clips Ah that the
de vídeos directos y clip Ah que la
photograph wasn't his m that he took it from
fotografía no era suya m que la cogió de
live videos and clips he didn't go to
vídeos directos y clips él no fue a
Malaga he didn't take that photo and it wasn't
Málaga no hizo esa foto y tampoco fue
with the intention of showing the license plate
con intención de enseñar la matrícula
like he says Ah that he didn't take the photograph
como dice Ah que la fotografía no la
with the intention of taking out the
hizo para con la intención de sacar la
license plate
matrícula
mm he didn't realize besides he didn't
mm no se dio cuenta además no se dio
realize he didn't realize
cuenta no se dio cuenta
Ah he didn't realize m and as soon as he
Ah no se dio cuenta m y en cuanto se lo
told him he deleted it and apologized yes yes yes yes
dijo lo borró y se disculpó sí sí sí sí
Well I think this tet tells the whole
Bueno yo creo que este tet dice toda la
truth in every sentence The only thing he
verdad en cada frase Solamente le ha
needed to say is that I exposed the license plate that I
faltado decir que que la matrícula la
put it up I published it
expuse yo que la puse yo la publiqué yo
and then I cried the thing I said and what he
y luego lloré la ha falta decí y lo de
blamed himself and then he deleted it is totally
que se culpó y luego lo borró totalmente
true without a doubt already  this family
cierto sin ninguna duda ya está familia
in the face of this that we are going to, the first thing that you
ante esto que vamos a yo lo primero que
see here is criticizing also a little not
aquí ven criticando también un poco no
denouncing a little some
denunciando un poco la algunos
comments on networks, a minor you
comentarios en redes una menor no se
cannot talk about a girl who has counted for so
puede hablar de una niña que tiene cuent
many days second give a diagnosis
tantos días segundo dar un diagnóstico
that I have seen tremendous mental gymnastics it
que he visto tremenda gimnasia mental no
is not mental gymnastics it is directly
es una gimnasia mental es directamente
an invention, I mean, neither the license plate is
un invento o sea ni la matrícula está
exposed everywhere nor the
expuesta por todos lados ni las
photographs were click and I don't know what
fotografías eran de click y de no sé qué
nor was an apology issued nor was it deleted it
ni ni se pidió disculpas ni se borró
is public yet but come on Estela
está público todavía pero vamos Estela
Eh I made it up and [ __ ] off for
Eh me lo invento y a tomar por culo por
throwing [ __ ] at Abi that's it and second
tirarle [__] a Abi ya está y segundo
I want to thank all my colleagues
Quiero agradecer a todos mis compañeros
but yesterday what Kiko Matamoros said how
pero ayer lo que dijo Kiko Matamoros qué
embarrassing what I wrote on Twitter I
vergüenza lo que escribí en Twitter ni
haven't even gotten involved but I trust him you
me he metido pero me fío de él vosotros
see it as
veis
normal that you put a mother
normal que a una madre la
or a father with his baby in a
pongáis o a un padre con su bebita en un
hospital no matter how much you dislike it
hospital por muy mal que os caiga
put yourselves in their place put yourselves in their place
poneros en su lugar poneros en su lugar
I am not saying that people but don't
yo no digo que la gente pero no
write such ugly things that I don't know what you are
escribáis cosas tan feas que no sé a qué
referring to here simply Bravo that
se refiere aquí simplemente Bravo que
Anabel I know that many people who
Anabel Yo sé que a mucha gente que le
dislike or like them want to
cae mal o le cae bien quiero dar las
thank  to my colleagues and my director
gracias a mis compañeros ya mis director
and my team because yesterday I felt very
y a mi equipo porque ayer me sentí muy
proud of the program that I work on with, how
orgullosa del programa que trabajo con
respectfully this topic was treated, things that there
qué respeto se trató este tema cosas que
are family channels, not all
hay cadenas familiares no todos los
programs that have also done very
programas que también lo han hecho muy
well but there are some collaborators who
bien pero hay algunos colaboradores que
have no idea or or or they tell what
no tienen ni idea o o o cuentan lo que
they are told there she is referring to
les cuentan ahí se está refiriendo a
Tele5 I don't know what specific comment she
tele5 no sé qué comentario en concreto
is criticizing but this was already
estará criticando pero ya esto fue
beastly Eh Lili sent this to me
bestial Eh Esto me lo ha mandado Lili
before doing the live show and this
antes de hacer el directo y esto me
seems like an outrage well not only does it
parece una barbaridad bueno no solamente
seem like an outrage to me It's that they are
es que me parezca una barbaridad Es que
going to I hope that we are going I
esto lo van a Yo espero que vamos me
imagine and I take for granted that they are going
imagino y doy por hecho que esto lo van
to report this or so this has been
a denunciar o sea esto según han
reported by sources close to the
informado Fuentes cercanas al hospital
Canarias 7 hospital the daughter of Anabel Pantoja
Canarias 7 la hija de Anabel Pantoja
Alma barely two months old began
alma de apenas dos meses de vida comenzó
to convulse and was taken to a
a convulsionar y fue llevada a un centro
hospital in Meloneras as she did not
hospitalario en meloneras como no
react she was intubated and
reaccionaba la intubaron y derivaron de
urgently referred to the maternal and child hospital in
urgencia al hospital materno infantil en
Las Palmas de Gran Canaria where she was
Las Palmas de Gran canaria donde fue
admitted last Friday
ingresada el pasado viernes por la
morning and where she is being
mañana y donde se le realiza un
closely monitored in the
seguimiento exhaustivo en la unidad de
intensive care unit  see
Medicina intensiva a ver
and you know what's happening with this that This is going to be
e sabéis qué pasa con esto que Esto va a
reported almost 100%
ser denunciado casi al 100%
eh or rather Canary Islands 7 Canary Islands 7 or rather
eh o sea Canarias 7 Canarias 7 o sea
This is going to be excuse me for a second they
Esto va a ser perdonadme un segundo que
're
me están
talking to me This is going to be reported
hablando Esto va a ser denunciado
Canary Islands 7 eh but but almost 100% eh
Canarias 7 eh pero pero casi al 100% eh
or rather realize that realize that it
o sea daros cuenta que daros cuenta que
could be true it could be a lie
puede ser verdad puede ser mentira no lo
I don't know I suspect it doesn't seem
sé yo sospecho a mí no me parece
reportable to me I think so I think it
denunciable Yo creo que sí yo creo que
could be true eh it could be a
sí puede ser verdad eh puede ser una
leak
filtración
from someone who works at the hospital you
e de alguien que trabaja en el hospital
know that journalists at most
ya sabéis que los periodistas a más
Canary Islands 7 don't I mean you know that
Canarias 7 no O sea ya sabes que los
journalists usually have contacts in the
periodistas suelen tener contactos en el
hospital
hospital
and they usually have people who leak
e y suelen tener gente que le filtren
things to them no or even maybe not
las cosas no o incluso a lo mejor no
someone from the hospital but someone
alguien del hospital sino alguien
close to the family who knows what's
cercano a la familia que sepa qué es lo
going on because I understand that there will
que est pasando porque yo entiendo que
be friends and there will be family members Who
habrá amistades y que habrá familiares
know what has happened what is not
Que sepan lo que ha pasado lo que no se
known yet is in the media
sabe todavía es en los medios de manera
officially but the thing is that you can't affirm
oficial pero es que tú no puedes afirmar
things about the health of a
cosas sobre la salud de un
baby I think eh remember for example
bebé yo creo eh acordaros de por ejemplo
the sentence that Maria
la la condena que le pusieron a María
Patiño received for talking about Maria's health to
Patiño por hablar de la salud de María a
Jose Campanario and then it turns out that
José campanario y luego Resulta ser que
and then it turns out that the
y luego Resulta ser que la que era
truth was not that she had it that it was something that she had
verdad no que lo tenía que era algo que
over time she recognized it but
tenía con el tiempo lo reconoció pero
of course you can't say it you can't
claro no puedes decirlo no puedes
tell it because that's exactly what she
contarlo pues eso mismo es lo que ha
reported gave ar rabar with the
denunciado dio ar rabar con la
leak eh sea I imagine I
filtración eh mar me imagino lo he
looked it up to see what she
mirado por encima para ver a qué se
meant with the leaked medical report
refería con lo del parte médico filtrado
eh but I don't know if it's very nice I don't
eh pero no sé yo si es muy agradable no
know you put yourself in the place
sé tú ponte en el lugar
everyone can work how they want eh
cada uno puede trabajar como quiera eh
but I don't know if it's very
pero no sé yo si es muy
nice to put that in a headline like that
agradable poner eso en un titular de esa
play with that not to have a
forma jugar con eso no para tener un
little bit more you could have
poquito más podrías Haber puesto
perfectly put what
perfectamente lo que hemos puesto
we have put not a serious complaint because of the
nosotros no grave denuncia por por el
state of health I don't know or a serious complaint
estado de salud No sé o grave denuncia
about Anabel's baby I don't know I'm
por la bebé de de Anabel no sé ya os
telling you eh I mean I'm not that
digo eh o sea yo no estoy tampoco tan en
against the headlines that
contra de los titulares que están
the colleagues are putting or how
poniendo los compañeros ni ni cómo se
the subject is being handled because I've
está llevando el tema porque que he
seen a little bit of the videos inside
bichado un poco los vídeos por dentro
okay seeing that there was so much commotion I've
vale al ver que había Tanto revuelo he
seen a little bit  the videos inside and I haven't
bichado un poco los vídeos por dentro y
seen any of them to see No, I haven't seen
de ninguno he visto a ver No no he visto
any nonsense maybe if I
ninguna barbaridad a lo mejor me yo si
were the family I might be a
fuera la familia Me podría molestar un
little or quite bothered by some headline like that
poco o bastante algún titular como eso
not the leaked one The medical report
no el de filtrado El parte médico
and they fear for his life That would bother me
e temen por su vida Eso me molestaría
but
pero
HM You know what happens Look the other
HM Es que sabéis qué pasa Mira el otro
day one as I was going to tell you before I
día uno como os iba a decir antes me ha
forgot the other day one justified it
olvidado el otro día uno lo justificaba
with comparing it to the
con el comparándolo con el tema de
Daniel Sancho issue the Daniel Sancho issue the
Daniel Sancho el tema de Daniel Sancho
first thing is that it's a true
lo primero es que es un true
crime the first thing is that it's a true crime
crime lo primero es que es un true crime
the second is that we're not talking about
lo segundo es que no estamos hablando de
a baby which I think is more sensitive than
un bebé que creo que es más sensible que
a crime between older people without
que un crimen entre personas mayores sin
taking away importance or weight of
quitarle importancia ni peso a por
course the
supuesto el
crime But I think it's more delicate I think it
crimen Pero creo que es más delicado
's more painful not what could be
creo que es más doloroso no lo que puede
happening maybe a family at
estar pasando a lo mejor una familia en
a time no I don't know but but it's not the
un momento no no lo sé pero pero no es
same in true crime and apart from that the
lo mismo en true crime y aparte el caso
Daniel Sancho case did have topics every day
Daniel Sancho sí que tenía temas todos
Uh I mean every day
los días Eh o sea todos los días salían
new things came out a new fact that he had
cosas nuevas un dato nuevo que había
bought here the bill for I don't know what the
comprado aquí la factura de no sé qué la
bill is not the same a true crime with
factura no es lo mismo un true crime con
a mystery behind what  has happened has not
un misterio detrás de qué ha pasado no
happened the versions of each one
ha pasado las versiones de cada uno no
is not the same as this that is one is a
es lo mismo que esto que es una es un
baby that has become ill it is not the
bebé que se ha puesto malito no es lo
same
mismo
regarding this I believe that yes eh I mean it is
respecto a esto yo creo que sí eh o sea
true Or it is a lie I believe that
sea verdad O sea mentira yo creo que
Canarias 7 will receive a complaint from
Canarias 7 recibirá una denuncia de
Anabel Pantoja eh I believe that yes
Anabel Pantoja eh yo creo que sí que
this is actionable I believe that this is
esto es demandable yo creo que esto es
actionable I mean you can give
demandable O sea tú puedes dar una
information that is of public interest
información que sea de interés público
about someone who is of public interest
sobre alguien que sea de interés público
no
no
eh Imagine the king The king is sick
eh Imagínate el rey El rey está enfermo
and the king is hospitalized and
y el rey está hospitalizado y se filtran
some data and some
algunos datos y algunas
things are leaked Well I think that you
cosas Pues yo creo que es que tú si
can report on the King's health No
puedes informar de la salud del Rey No
if you find out or suspect no I don't know I think that is
si te enteras o sospechas no no sé creo
not the way the truth I think
que no es la forma la verdad creo que
this is actionable It's that we have it we
esto es demandable Es que tenemos la
have the example of what happened to
tenemos tenemos el ejemplo de de lo de
María José Campanario no I mean they
María José campanario no O sea
condemned María Patio and they didn't look at whether it
condenaron a María patio y no se miró si
was true or a lie they looked at that she had
era verdad o era mentira se miró que que
taken something out of her privacy about
había sacado una cosa de su intimidad de
her health So why would it be legal
su salud Entonces por qué va ser legal
for someone to bring up the topic about the health
que alguien saque tema sobre la salud
of Anabel Pantoja's baby man
del bebé de Anabel Pantoja hombre
dolores I don't think he says dolores  We'll see if
dolores No creo dice dolores veremos si
the mother says it exclusively, damn it. I do
lo dice la madre en exclusiva [__] No
n't think she'll do an exclusive with that,
creo no que haga una exclusiva con eso
because then my
es que entonces ya se me caerían los
balls would fall off. People are here pointing out
[__] está aquí la gente señalando a
the youtubers for this headline, for this
los youtubers por este titular por esta
amount of video, for this live stream, and
cantidad de vídeo por este directo y de
suddenly she appears in an exclusive
repente que salga ella en una exclusiva
on the cover of reading, well, my
en la portada de lectura vamos se me
balls fall off.
caen los huevos